youthedesigner.com 2011-02-18

# Privacy Policy

## COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY

Digital Room, Inc. understands the importance of protecting the privacy of YouTheDesigner.com users. The information collected on the YouTheDesigner.com website is used to market and improve the services we and our subsidiaries offer, to improve the YouTheDesigner.com web site content, and to contact you with updates to the web site or for other marketing purposes.

Certain areas of YouTheDesigner.com, including those areas used to make purchases, require registration and/or a password for access. Information obtained from registered users of these areas may also be used for YouTheDesigner.com marketing purposes, and cookies may be used in those and other areas, as is described in this Policy. Information obtained in these areas may also be used in accordance with agreements governing access to and use of the specific areas. In addition, visitors to YouTheDesigner.com will need to register for a YouTheDesigner.com Login user ID and password to use many of the interactive features on YouTheDesigner.com as well as to make a purchase or file an order from YouTheDesigner.com. Log file data and other information gathered from registered users of YouTheDesigner.com are used to improve the YouTheDesigner.com customer experience.

For more information on this Privacy Policy, please read below.

  * Visitor Information
  * Personal Information
  * Use of Personal Information
  * Cookies
  * Links
  * Security
  * Opt Out Options
  * How do I contact YouTheDesigner.com

## Visitor Information

The YouTheDesigner.com web server uses an extended log file format which captures: date and time of visit, referring address (location from which a visitor comes to YouTheDesigner.com), type of Internet browser, and visitor’s IP address. (Each computer that connects to the Internet is assigned a unique number, an IP address, for identification purposes). The log file does not capture a visitor’s email address.

## Personal Information

Certain areas of YouTheDesigner.com ask for personal information. YouTheDesigner.com uses this personal information to aid in presenting its customers with a better interactive experience and to facilitate the customerís ability to make purchases and orders from the YouTheDesigner.com website. To register for a login user ID, your name, address, email address, billing information, and business profile are requested. This information is collected to help us further develop our services, to provide you access to valuable YouTheDesigner.com Internet-based information and services, and to facilitate the billing process for those services if you elect to use them. Customers will have the ability to access and change the information which they have provided to YouTheDesigner.com by use of the appropriate features on the YouTheDesigner.com website.

## Use of Personal Information

The information collected through this site helps us identify the type of web site content that our customers value, allowing us to market and improve the web site and our services. The information is also used to send email notifications to customers about updates to the web site, and to contact customers by other means for marketing and other purposes. Our policy is to not give, sell or otherwise distribute the information collected through this site to third parties outside of Digital Room, Inc. and its subsidiaries (unless required by law); provided, however, in some cases we may use suppliers to assist us in collecting, using or otherwise processing for our benefit the information obtained through this site. YouTheDesigner.com does use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. Our practice is to require our suppliers and vendors to conduct themselves in a manner consistent with this policy and our requirements.

## Information From Third Parties

If necessary, YouTheDesigner.com obtains consumer information from third-party providers in order to improve the accuracy of our customer database and to increase our understanding of our customers or to identify potential customers. For example, we get updated addresses from the National Change of Address (NCOA) service to assist us in having the correct addresses for our customers.

## Cookies

A cookie is a series of data characters that, when programmed into a web site, is placed by the web server into the browser’s application folder on your computer. Once placed onto your machine, the cookie will allow the web site to “recognize” you as a unique individual. YouTheDesigner.com uses these Coolies to personalize information for certain segments of its customer base. Secondly, in some instances, cookies are used to allow YouTheDesigner.com the opportunity to associate individual customers with their information profiles. For example, through the use of cookies, YouTheDesigner.com can “remember” your user ID when you login to YouTheDesigner.com on your computer. Should you choose to do so, cookies can be removed from your hard drive and certain web browsers can be set so that cookies are not used or saved. Please check with your browser provider for more information on removing cookies.

## Links

Our sites may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware of this fact when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that they visit which collects personally-identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.

## Security

For the safety of our customers who are shopping online, YouTheDesigner.com always has security measures in place to protect customer information. YouTheDesigner.com takes all reasonable precautions to protect against the loss, misuse and unauthorized access of your personal information under our control. Because the security of your personal information is a high priority, we have taken numerous steps to ensure that it is processed confidentially, accurately and securely. The YouTheDesigner.com web site uses encryption technology, such as Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology, which is supported by the vast majority of modern Internet browsers. SSL technology represents the highest level of security available on the Internet, automatically encrypting information traveling over the Internet, verifying the identity of the transacting servers through certificates and digital signatures, and confirming that the integrity of the message content is maintained throughout its transmission. YouTheDesigner.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us by e-mail, and you do so at your own risk.

## Opt Out Options

YouTheDesigner.com allows customers the option to opt-out of marketing communications upon request. Once we receive your information, we may send you marketing communications that contain valuable offers, promotions and other content. However, users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by following the directions contained in the communication. All marketing communications from YouTheDesigner.com will tell you how to stop receiving them. In addition, you can opt out of receiving further marketing communications from YouTheDesigner.com by the use of the Unsubscribe page on the YouTheDesigner.com website.

## How do I contact YouTheDesigner.com?

Our postal address is:  
YouTheDesigner.com  
Digital Room, Inc.  
10936 Santa Monica Blvd.  
Los Angeles, CA 90025

We can be reached via email at info@YouTheDesigner.com or by telephone at (888) 888-4211.

Digital Room, Inc. reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time with or without notice. Please check back frequently in the event of changes.

Your use of YouTheDesigner.com constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy.
